[    
    {        
        "name" : "La Famiglia",       
        "tags":"Italian", 
        
        "lang": "en",       
        "term": [            
            {                
                "question": "Mother",                
                "answer": "mamma"            
            },            
            {                
                "question" : "Father",                
                "answer" : "papa"            
            },            
            {                
                "question": "Brother",                
                "answer": "fratello"            
            },            
            {                
                "question" : "Sister",                
                "answer" : "sorella"            
            },            
            {                
                "question": "Grandpa",                
                "answer": "nonno"            
            },            {                
                "question" : "Grandma",                
                "answer" : "nonna"            
            },            
            {                
                "question" : "Parents",                
                "answer" : "genitori"            
            }        
        ]
    },
    {
        "name": "Verbo Essere",
        "tags": "Italian",
        
        "lang": "it",
        "term": [
            {
               "question" : "Io",
               "answer": "Sono"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Tu",
                "answer": "sei"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Lui",
                "answer": "è"
             },
             {
                 "question" : "Lei",
                 "answer": "è"
             },
             {
                "question" : "Noi",
                "answer": "siamo"
             },
             {
                 "question" : "Voi",
                 "answer": "siete"
             },
             {
                "question" : "Loro",
                "answer": "Sono"
             }
             
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "name": "YCT 5 - Lesson 1",
        
        "tags": "Chinese",
        "lang": "ch",
        "term": [
            {
               "question" : "功夫",
               "answer": "Kung Fu"
            },
            {
                "question" : "非常",
                "answer": "extremely"
            },
            {
                "question" : "特别",
                "answer": "especially"
             },
             {
                 "question" : "我喜欢帮助别人。",
                 "answer": "I like to help others"
             },
             {
                "question" : "对。。。感兴趣",
                "answer": "Be intrested in"
             },
             {
                 "question" : "飞",
                 "answer": "fly"
             },
             {
                "question" : "当然",
                "answer": "of course"
             },
             {
                "question": "厉害",
                "answer": "awesome"
             },
             {
                "question" : "和。。。一样",
                "answer" : "same as"
             },
             {
                "question": "帮助",
                "answer": "help"
             },
             {
                "question" : "别人",
                "answer" : "other people"
             },
             {
                "question": "阿宝",
                "answer": "po"
             },
             {
                "question" : "我对功夫特别感兴趣。",
                "answer" : "I am extremely interested in studying Chinese."
             },
             {
                "question" : "我和妈妈一样都喜欢吃鸡肉。",
                "answer": "I like chicken as same as my mom"
             }
             
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "name": "YCT 5 - Lesson 2",
        "tags": "Chinese",
        "lang": "ch",
        
        "term": [
            {
               "question" : "大象",
               "answer": "elephant"
            },
            {
                "question" : "兔子",
                "answer": "rabbit"
            },
            {
                "question" : "蝴蝶",
                "answer": "butterfly"
             },
             {
                 "question" : "虫子",
                 "answer": "worm"
             },
             {
                "question" : "矮",
                "answer": "short"
             },
             {
                 "question" : "胖",
                 "answer": "fat"
             },
             {
                "question" : "短",
                "answer": "duan"
             },
             {
                "question": "更",
                "answer": "even more"
             },
             {
                "question" : "讨厌",
                "answer" : "dislike"
             },
             {
                "question": "告诉",
                "answer": "gaosu"
             },
             {
                "question" : "将来",
                "answer" : "future"
             },
             {
                "question": "长长",
                "answer": "long"
             },
             {
                "question" : "兔子更可爱。",
                "answer" : "The  rabbit is cuter"
             }
             
            
        ]
    }
]
